# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)


# quizs = Quiz.create([
#   {
#     title: "HTML",
#     description:"HTML basic course"
#   },
#   {
#     title: "CSS",
#     description:"CSS basic course"
#   },
#   {
#     title: "SQL",
#     description:"SQL basic course"
#   },
#   {
#     title: "Ruby",
#     description:"Ruby basic course"
#   },
#   {
#     title: "JavaScript",
#     description:"Javascript basic course"
#   },
#   {
#     title: "React",
#     description:"React basic course"
#   }
# ])


# questions = Question.create([
#   {
#     question: "HTML",
#     correct_answer:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_1:"HTML basic courseasdafa",
#     answer_2:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_3:"HTML basic courseasasfaf",
#     answer_4:"HTML basic courseasdasfafa",
#     quiz_id:1
#   },
#   {
#     question: "HTML",
#     correct_answer:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_1:"HTML basic courseasfasfa",
#     answer_2:"HTML basic courseasfasf",
#     answer_3:"HTML basic courseasdafs",
#     answer_4:"HTML basic course",
#     quiz_id:1
#   },
#   {
#     question: "HTML",
#     correct_answer:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_1:"HTML basic courseasfafaf",
#     answer_2:"HTML basic courseasafs",
#     answer_3:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_4:"HTML basic courseasdafsaf",
#     quiz_id:1
#   },
#   {
#     question: "HTML",
#     correct_answer:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_1:"HTML basic coursefasfasf",
#     answer_2:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_3:"HTML basic courseasafsa",
#     answer_4:"HTML basic courseasfafafs",
#     quiz_id:1
#   },
#   {
#     question: "HTML",
#     correct_answer:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_1:"HTML basic coursessdfsdfsf",
#     answer_2:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_3:"HTML basic coursesdfsfd",
#     answer_4:"HTML basic course sdfsfd",
#     quiz_id:1
#   },
#   {
#     question: "HTML",
#     correct_answer:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_1:"HTML basic course",
#     answer_2:"HTML basic course not",
#     answer_3:"HTML basic course not",
#     answer_4:"HTML basic course not",
#     quiz_id:1
#   }
# ])


# questions = Question.create([
#     {
#         question: 'Which of the following scripts will run successfully',
#         correct_answer: 'SELECT `customer name` FROM customers WHERE cat_id = 12 ORDER BY cat_id;',
#         answer_1: 'Users statistics SELECT customer name FROM customers;',
#         answer_2: 'SELECT `customer name` FROM customers WHERE cat_id = 12 ORDER BY cat_id;',
#         answer_3: "SELECT FROM `customers` 'customer name';",
#         answer_4: 'SELECT `customer name` FROM customers ORDER BY zone WHERE cat_id = 12;',
#         quiz_id: 3
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'Which keyword is used with the ALTER command to delete a column?',
#         correct_answer: 'DROP',
#         answer_1: 'DROP',
#         answer_2: 'DELETE',
#         answer_3: 'REMOVE',
#         answer_4: 'CHANGE',
#         quiz_id: 3
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'Commands passed to the MySQL daemon are written in',
#         correct_answer: 'The Structured Query Language',
#         answer_1: 'English',
#         answer_2: 'The Structured Query Language',
#         answer_3: 'Your Choice From Perl, PHP, Java Or Some Other Languages',
#         answer_4: 'Swedish',
#         quiz_id: 3
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'MySQL workbench decreases the productivity of a MySQL developer compared to other server access tools such as phpMyAdmin?',
#         correct_answer: 'False',
#         answer_1: 'True',
#         answer_2: 'False',
#         answer_3: 'Both',
#         answer_4: "None of Above",
#         quiz_id: 3
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'Can you start two MySQL servers at one PC?',
#         correct_answer: 'True',
#         answer_1: 'True',
#         answer_2: 'False',
#         answer_3: 'Both',
#         answer_4: "None of Above",
#         quiz_id: 3
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'MySQL supports different Character Sets, which command is used to display all of them?',
#         correct_answer: 'SHOW CHARACTER SET',
#         answer_1: 'SHOW;  ;',
#         answer_2: 'None Of The Mentioned',
#         answer_3: 'CHARACTER SET;',
#         answer_4: 'SHOW CHARACTER SET',
#         quiz_id: 3
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'Is the NULL value treated as 0?',
#         correct_answer: 'False',
#         answer_1: 'True',
#         answer_2: 'False',
#         answer_3: 'Both',
#         answer_4: "None of Above",
#         quiz_id: 3
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'The command to remove rows from a table "MOVIE" is:',
#         correct_answer: 'DROP FROM MOVIE',
#         answer_1: 'REMOVE FROM MOVIE',
#         answer_2: 'DROP FROM MOVIE',
#         answer_3: 'DELETE FROM MOVIE WHERE',
#         answer_4: 'UPDATE FROM MOVIE',
#         quiz_id: 3
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'Which command is used to modify column names or table structure?',
#         correct_answer: 'ALTER',
#         answer_1: 'MODIFY',
#         answer_2: 'ADD',
#         answer_3: 'CHANGE',
#         answer_4: 'ALTER',
#         quiz_id: 3
#       },
#       {
#         question: "To use MySQL on your computer, you'll need",
#         correct_answer: 'Some Sort Of Client Program To Access The Databases',
#         answer_1: 'Perl, PHP Or Java',
#         answer_2: 'FTP And Telnet',
#         answer_3: 'Some Sort Of Client Program To Access The Databases',
#         answer_4: 'A Browser',
#         quiz_id: 3
#       }
# ])



# questions = Question.create([
#     {
#         question: '#!/bin/bash is commonly called as',
#         correct_answer: 'shebang',
#         answer_1: 'shebang',
#         answer_2: 'hashbang',
#         answer_3: 'Script Initialiser',
#         answer_4: 'None of the Above',
#         quiz_id: 18
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'Which command can you use to re-execute a previous command?',
#         correct_answer: '!!',
#         answer_1: '!cat',
#         answer_2: '!!',
#         answer_3: '!a',
#         answer_4: '!3',
#         quiz_id: 18
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'How can you set the default rwx permission to all users on every file which is created in the current shell?',
#         correct_answer: 'umask  0777',
#         answer_1: 'umask  0777',
#         answer_2: 'chmod  777',
#         answer_3: 'chown  777',
#         answer_4: 'umask  0666',
#         quiz_id: 18
#       },
#       {
#         question: 'How to list the contents of a folder?',
#         correct_answer: 'ls',
#         answer_1: 'pwd',
#         answer_2: 'ls',
#         answer_3: 'list',
#         answer_4: 'print',
#         quiz_id: 18
#       }
# ])


# questions = Question.create([
#     {
#         question: 'What does CSS stand for?',
#         correct_answer: 'Cascading Style Sheets  ',
#         answer_1: 'Computer Style Sheets  ',
#         answer_2: 'Colorful Style Sheets',
#         answer_3: 'Cascading Style Sheets  ',
#         answer_4: 'Creative Style Sheets',
#         quiz_id: 18
#       }
# ])